<resources>
    <string name="app_name">E-snap</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_challenge">NewChallenge</string>


    <!--Transportation tips-->


    <string name="t_tip1">Plan out your meals at the start of the week so you can reduce your trips food shopping.</string>
    <string name="t_tip2">Carpool to work, school, and events with friends.</string>
    <string name="t_tip3">Look up the public transit in your city and state. You will help the environment AND save on gas and parking!</string>
    <string name="t_tip4">Carpool to work, school, and events with friends.</string>
    <string name="t_tip5">Tempted to turn up the AC or heat in the car? Try rolling down your windows (or bringing gloves).</string>
    <string name="t_tip6">Inspect your car tire pressure and inflate them to the recommended pressure to reduce energy use.</string>
    <string name="t_tip7">Going out to dinner or ice cream? Try biking there to really earn your meal!</string>

    <string-array name="trans_array">
        <item>@string/t_tip1</item>
        <item>@string/t_tip2</item>
        <item>@string/t_tip3</item>
        <item>@string/t_tip4</item>
        <item>@string/t_tip5</item>
        <item>@string/t_tip6</item>
        <item>@string/t_tip7</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_accepted_challenge">AcceptedChallenge</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cooling">Cooling</string>
    <string name="title_activity_food">Food</string>
    <string name="title_activity_favorites">Favorites</string>

    <string name="h_tip1">Set your favorite pair of cozy socks by the door, and throw them on when you first return home, as feet retain little heat on their own.</string>
    <string name="h_tip2">Getting ready to catch some zzz\'s? Take a minute to draw the blinds, which act like a blanket for your house.</string>
    <string name="h_tip3">Grab a cup of cocoa or cinnamon tea, turn on some Nat King Cole, and enjoy some good company and winter spirit tonight! A gas stove is actually the most efficient way to boil the water, and electric kettles are good too.</string>
    <string name="h_tip4">Spontaneous week-end getaway? Sounds dope. Adjust the thermostat to 55 deg F on your way out the door.</string>
    <string name="h_tip5">We humans sleep better at temperatures between 61 and 65 deg F. Either manually or set thermostat to automatically reduce temperatures as you wind down to bed.</string>
    <string name="h_tip6">Beanies are a worthy investment.</string>
    <string name="h_tip7"> If radiators are located near cold outside walls, place a sheet of
aluminum foil between the radiator and the wall to reflect heat
back into the room</string>
    <string name="h_tip8">The warmest air in a room will rise to the ceiling. Turning a ceiling fan on at low speeds will actually make the air feel warmer without any additional heating.</string>

    <string-array name="heat_array">
        <item>@string/h_tip1</item>
        <item>@string/h_tip2</item>
        <item>@string/h_tip3</item>
        <item>@string/h_tip4</item>
        <item>@string/h_tip5</item>
        <item>@string/h_tip6</item>
        <item>@string/h_tip7</item>
        <item>@string/h_tip8</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="c_tip1">If using window units, install your AC in a shady location. This will make you cool and efficient. Who doesn\'t want that?</string>
    <string name="c_tip2">Buy an easy-to-drink, spill-proof water bottle and keep it filled with iced water. One 24oz bottle of ice water will instantly provide relief from the summer heat.</string>
    <string name="c_tip3">Are you a guy? Well us women actually prefer room temperatures of about 5 deg F warmer, so turn down the AC if women are visiting. Thanks from all of us.</string>
    <string name="c_tip4">Take a cool shower in the morning. This has been shown to help wake you up when caffeine is out of reach. Saving of cooling and water heating bills too? Cool stuff.</string>
    <string name="c_tip5">Operate your stove, oven, dishwasher and clothes dryer in the
morning or evening when it\’s cooler outside. They add extra
heat to your home and make your air conditioner work harder</string>
    <string name="c_tip6">Hitting the road? Driving with the windows down in place of air conditioning when below 40 mph can bring in big energy savings.</string>
    <string name="c_tip7"> Set the air conditioning thermostat at 78 degrees during the
day when home and higher when away</string>

    <string-array name="cool_array">
        <item>@string/c_tip1</item>
        <item>@string/c_tip2</item>
        <item>@string/c_tip3</item>
        <item>@string/c_tip4</item>
        <item>@string/c_tip5</item>
        <item>@string/c_tip6</item>
        <item>@string/c_tip7</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
